Do you want me to include it?
入れて欲しいですか?
picture?
え?
I guess I know...
知っちゃうなぁ...
a little bit ...
ちょっと ...
Sorry, it's been a while.
ごめんなさい、久しぶりです
Aren't you nervous?
緊張してないですか?
It's been a while, so just a little.
久しぶりだから、ちょっと
Lose.
負 け
What do you think of this costume I prepared for you today?
今日僕が用意したこの衣装、どうですか?
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Not enough color?
色が足らない?
Not enough.
足らない
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It suits you so well.
めちゃめちゃ似合ってますね
Definitely near-ho.
絶対ニアホやろな
I prepared this costume, but let's make the chest area a little tighter.
この衣装を用意したんですけど、 ちょっと胸元グイッとこう
Embarrassing, embarrassing.
恥ずかしい恥ずかしい
That's wonderful.
素晴らしいなぁ
I want to do it on a trip.
旅行でやりたい
What do you think?
どうですか?
I prepared it for the first time in about a month,
約1ヶ月ぶりに用意したんですけど、
Something like this...
なんか こう...
What's wrong with finding a good man?
良い男ができたところ、 何かないんですか?
There's nothing.
何もないですね
there is nothing.
何もない
Does that mean you're not wearing this costume?
ってことは、 この衣装をしてないってことですか?
it is...
それは...
secret.
秘密
That's the same secret as before,
前もその秘密とかそうなんですけど、
That means they are equal, right?
それは、 イコールしてますよってことですよね
I guess so.
うんだろう
he
彼
's skin is white, isn't it?
の 肌は白いですよね
Can I have you stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってもらっていいですか?
Her chest is amazing.
胸元がすごい
amazing.
すごい
Do you remember the old man from the other day?
この間のおじさんを覚えてますか?
Yeah.
うん
How was it?
どうでしたか?
Are you doing it?
してるんですか?
Remember.
思い出して
How was it?
どうでした?
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I went there with a lot of bags.
バッグでいっぱい行ってましたもんね
hey.
ね
Did you remember?
思い出したんですか?
Yeah.
うん
I remembered.
思い出した
Are you touching it?
触ってるんですか?
Are you still doing well?
相変わらず元気?
fine?
元気?
Yeah.
うん
Do you want it to come in soon?
早く入れてほしいんですか?
Yeah.
うん
hey.
ね
I'll know.
知っちゃうなぁ
I should know
知っちゃ
cormorant.
う
He said he feels good facing the camera.
カ メラに向かって気持ちいいですって
It feels good.
気 持ちいいです
feeling
気持ち
good.
いい
I went there many times.
バ ッグ何回も行っちゃった
Next is this.
次はこっち
I'll make you feel good.
気持ちよくしてあげる
It seems to feel really good.
すごい気持ちよさそうなんですね
Remember
覚 えて
I asked.
た んだ
Uncle's weakness
おじさんの弱いところ
A lot of sperm is produced.
に 精子がいっぱい作られてる
Cheating on PE a lot.
体育をいっぱい騙してね
Let me help you a little
手 を少々してもらって
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
What does the next uncle taste like?
次 の1回目のおじさんの味は?
Yeah.
うん
It's not very tasty.
あまり美味しくない
Yeah.
うん
I really like it when you wear this costume.
この衣装着てもらって やっぱ似合いますね
I saw a lot of uncle's stuff just now.
さっきおじさんの いっぱい出てたけど
The voice was coming out.
声のが出てた
What do you think, uncle's voice sperm?
どうですか、おじさんの声精子
bad.
まずい
You can put out more, right?
もっと出せるでしょ
dangerous.
あぶない
Oh, your hands are soft.
あら、お手柔らかい
Feels good.
いい感じ
Can I have your pants on too?
パンツも乗せてもらっていいですか?
hold your hand here, here
ここに手を持って、こっち
Take it with you.
を 持って
Can you move in a way that makes you feel comfortable?
自分で気持ちいいふうに動いてくれる?
Just put your upper body hands up like the 4 cases, and move like this.
そのまま上半身の手を立てて 4つの場合みたいにして これで動
Can you do it?
ける?
In the middle.
その 中途